

#### DEED LEADNING R&D ENGINEER

22 Square Louis Armand, 35000, Rennes, France

□ (+33) 6-4647-0816 | Marchang@irisa.fr | Archangheng19931123.github.io | Drangheng19931123 | Drangheng19

"Maximum effort!"

### About Me\_\_

I am a second year PhD student in <u>LACODAM</u> team at <u>INRIA Rennes</u> laboratory. I am working under the supervision of <u>Prof. Elisa FROMONT</u> and <u>Prof. Sébastien LEFEVRE</u>. In the same time, I work as a Deep learning R&D Engineer at <u>ATERMES</u> in Paris. My current research interest is deep learning for multispectral object detection, small object detection and video object detection.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

ATERMES Paris area, France

DEEP LEARNING R&D ENGINEER

Dec 2018 - now

- Built Deep Learning models for accurate object detection (car, pedestrian, bicycle, etc) at long distance (>3km).
- Fusing information from multiple sensors (thermal camera & visible camera) to improve the detection precision.
- Model inference acceleration for efficient deep learning applications on embedded systems.

#### **Hubert Curien laboratory**

Saint-étienne, France

APPRENTICESHIP Sep. 2017 - Oct. 2018

- · Implement different deep learning models for face/person detection in public transport (bus, tramway, subway, etc).
- Proposed efficient video object detection methods for video surveillance applications.

## **Education**

INRIA Rennes Rennes, France

PHD STUDENT IN DEEP LEARNING AND COMPUTER VISION

Dec. 2018 - now

- Subject: Multispectral Object detection for all-day video surveillance.
- Industry-oriented PhD program, cooperation with ATERMES company.

**Télécom Saint-étienne**Saint-étienne, France

ENGINEER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER VISION AND IMAGE PROCESSING

Sep. 2015 - Oct. 2018

One-year Apprenticeship in Hubert Curien laboratory.

Xidian University Xi'an, China

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2016

### **Publications**

### Localize to Classify and Classify to Localize: Mutual Guidance in Object Detection [pdf]

Kyoto, Japan

15TH ASIAN CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION (ACCV2020)

Dec. 2020

We propose a new anchor matching criterion guided, during the training phase, by the optimization of both the localization and the classification tasks: the predictions related to one task are used to dynamically assign sample anchors and improve the model on the other task, and
vice versa. This strategy significantly improves the object detection accuracy of different deep learning architectures on PASCAL VOC and MS

### Multispectral Fusion for object detection with Cyclic Fuse-and-Refine blocks [pdf]

Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

27TH IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON IMAGE PROCESSING (ICIP2020)

Oct. 2020

We propose a new feature fusion method for neural networks that leverages the complementary/consistency balance existing in multispectral
features by adding to the network architecture, a particular module that cyclically fuses and refines each spectral feature. We obtain state-ofthe-art results on KAIST Multispectral pedestrian detection benchmark.

#### Improving video object detection by Seq-Bbox Matching [pdf]

Prague, Czech Republic

14TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION THEORY AND APPLICATIONS (VISAPP2019)

Feb. 2019

• We propose a novel and highly effective box-level post-processing method to improve the accuracy of video object detection. The proposed method can be applied to online/offline detection. It achieves state-of-the-art performance on ImageNet VID dataset.